George Constant
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Photographic Material, 1912-1978, Series 4:
  - Photographs of Oil Paintings, Children, 1937-1942 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of Oil Paintings, Portraits, Trios, circa 1920s (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of Oil Paintings, Women, 1923-1946 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of Pen and Ink Drawings, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Sculpture and Fabric Art, circa 1910-1920s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of Watercolors, Abstracts and Block Forms, circa 1940-1960s (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Watercolors, Animals and Flowers, circa 1930-1940s (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Watercolors, Female Nudes, circa 1920-1960s (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Watercolors, Female Nudes Seated, circa 1930-1950s (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Watercolors, Figures Seated, circa 1940s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of Watercolors, Landscapes, circa 1940s (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of Watercolors, Portraits, circa 1930-1950s (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Slides of Oils, Watercolors, Pen/Ink, Pencil, and Drypoints, circa 1930-1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)